What is it?
Nothing! Just thinking,
"wow, I'm really an idol!"
All done!
So pretty!
Fun in Just a Minute!
Ultimate Trivia
You two look motivated.
Good morning!
Oh! Good morning, ma'am!
Are you all ready?
Yes!
Why did I get roped into this...?
Lilly wanted us all to be here!
Lulu wouldn't have debuted without her help.
This show is so much fun!
I watch it every week!
Me too!
I do too!
It's super rare we all get
to work together on something!
And a TV appearance will
bring more gigs to the agency!
I guess you're right.
Good luck out there!
Thank you!
Is Rin-chan ready to go?
Yes.
Mom
Hello?
Will you be over on Saturday?
It's your grandmother's birthday.
Can't, I have work.
You have to. We already ordered catering.
We're about to go live. I'm hanging up.
What's wrong?
Same as always.
Please get on standby!
Okay!
Let's go!
I can't wait!
I'll do my best!
Let's go make our mark!
Yeah!
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Bae, bae, bae
Bubee, bubee
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Magical Sisters LuluttoLilly
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
Magical Sisters LuluttoLilly
My heart is racing like crazy
And right before my eyes
Are the colors of a brand new world
Whoa
Stay with me today
We'll walk hand in hand
Dreaming of the place where we can become light
I can hear the magic
I wanna sing with you
Let's sing together
You're a bright shining star
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
We can be shining stars
Forever and ever
That's our secret magic
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Bae, bae, bae
Bubee, bubee
B-U-B-E-E, bubee
Bubee love
Welcome to Hell's Quiz
What waits beyond the vast seas ahead?
Treasure on the Waves
This week, we'll set off
on yet another epic journey.
The quiz show Treasure on the Waves
is brought to you live.
We're your hosts, Bernard Kento...
And Wataya Rin. We hope you enjoy!
Let's meet our contestants!
These four guests all come from
the idol agency Production Once More!
I'm Toko, the reliable big sis of Once More!
I'm Sena. I handle our looks.
W-With the singing voice of an angel...
Lu-lu-lu-lu-lu...
I'm Lulu, and I love to sing!
I'm the youngest member of the agency,
the always energetic Lilly!
Thank you for having us!
These new idols have been making a big splash!
How will they do on our show?
I can't wait to find out!
Now, allow me to explain the rules!
Every time you get a question right,
you progress 1 mile.
The first person to reach
the treasure island wins.
WIN
All of you are competing
to get the treasure!
The victor will get this treasure chest trophy.
Now the quiz will begin!
Let's see our first question.
Here it is!
In a survey conducted this year
at elementary schools nationwide,
what job ranked #1 in careers
children want to pursue in their future?
In a survey conducted this year at elementary schools nationwide, what job ranked #1 in careers children want to pursue in their future?
How does this work?
You write the answer here.
Elementary school...
It's just how it looks on TV!
Now, present your answers one at a time!
Obviously, it's an idol!
A patissier?
I know!
It's a manga artist!
A civil servant, maybe?
And the answer is...
Manga artist!
Yay!
You sure know a lot
about elementary schoolers.
Yeah.
Well done, Lilly-san!
Thanks! I've got this!
The battle's only just begun.
Lilly-san advances 1 mile!
Next is a Close-Up Quiz!
What is shown in this footage?
Contestants, present your answers!
Outer space!
A fancy squid.
A mizu manju!
Lilly-san, Lulu-san, that's correct!
Wow, we got it at the same time!
Good for us!
Mizu manju...?
What's that?
Let's look at the footage.
As you can see, the correct answer is...
Mizu manju
mizu manju, a confection
known for its delicious jiggly texture!
That's too hard.
Where the heck did "fancy squid" come from?
Well, look at it. It's see-through.
Well done, both of you!
Both of you progress 1 mile!
Now for a team battle!
Drawing Telephone Quiz
Drawing Telephone Quiz!
The rules are simple.
You must draw a prompt
to get it across to the next person.
If the last person can guess the prompt correctly,
all players progress 1 mile.
Correct
Will the prompt make it to the end?
It's hippo. Hippo.
Hippo
Got it!
Lulu-chan!
Hippo
Here it is, Sena-san.
Let's see.
Toko.
Alright.
What on earth...?
Now, present the answer!
Let's see Toko's drawing!
What the heck...
What in the world is this?
S...Seaweed-Man?
Like some sort of superhero
from Seaweed Planet?
Never heard of it, but...
Unfortunately, that is incorrect.
The correct answer is "hippo"!
Huh?!
Hippo
That's a hippo!
Yeah, that's a hippo.
That can't be a hippo!
You must've made a mistake
and drawn some sort of new monster, right?
Lulu-san, your art is certainly unique!
Things are starting to heat up!
Lilly got a head start on
Treasure on the Waves...
Where's Bernard?
Lilly-san gets it right!
Just behind her in second place is Lulu-san!
They're doing good.
I wonder who will win!
Sena-san is correct!
Lulu-san and Lilly-san are correct!
Yeah!
Let's review the rankings so far!
Currently in first place is Lilly-san!
Sweet!
And in last place is Toko-san.
Give me the bonus quiz!
Afraid we can't do that.
Aw, man...
It's no fun if it ends this way!
Lililula palilula,
make things even more exciting!
Huh? What's going on?
Treasure on the Waves
Hell's Quiz
What the? What the?!
Now, it's time for...
Hell's Quiz to begin!
Get the question wrong,
and you'll fall into the sea of lava,
where you'll set sail for hell!
Hell?!
What's all this?
They didn't mention this at all.
Oh no, my magic's out of control again!
Oh dear, Lilly misfired again!
That looks bad.
What's going on? None of this is in the script!
I'll go check.
For now, guide them using cue cards.
Will do!
What is the meaning of all this?
I'm terribly sorry.
What on earth is he up to?
Dude, what's going on?
Some new segment?
Just keep going!
H-Hello, viewers!
Our program is produced with utmost safety in mind,
so please do not be concer—
Time to break open the gates of hell!
Hold on a minute!
Four glass floors remain.
4 glass floors remain
So hot!
You're kidding.
We'll be okay... right?
Toko, what do we do?
I'm sure this is just staged.
But it'll be pretty bad if we fall.
It's, err, gotten pretty fun, huh?
Now, the Hell's Quiz.
Here's the question.
Nebuchadnezzar II, the son of Nabopolassar,
rebuilt Babylon in the 6th century BC.
What is the name of the structure
said to be built by him for the queen?
I'm sorry?
Th-That's a pretty tough question...
State your answer.
The Hanging Gardens.
Oh. That's correct.
Wow! How'd you know that?
It was in the trivia book
I was reading backstage.
That's amazing!
You got it right...
but since everyone else got it wrong...
you'll all fall down one floor!
That's dangerous!
You're going too far!
This isn't what I had in mind!
Lulu-san, well done getting the answer!
I guess I made the question too easy.
I'll try to make the next quiz even harder to answer.
Knock it off!
The "What Are Idols Into?" Quiz!
Huh? That's my phone!
Here's the question!
What has Toko-san gotten into searching lately?
Don't tell me...
It wasn't me!
He wasn't kidding. This is hard to answer.
I'm sorry, Toko-san!
What's happening?
If you don't answer,
you will fall another floor!
Here's a hint: it's something
she's struggling with!
Oh no...
Is it what I think it is?
Or wait... not that!
I don't remember, but it can't be good!
State your answer!
"Tricks to getting smarter".
Sorry, but that's wrong!
I'm not dumb!
That's something you struggle with, no?
State your answer!
"How to be less shy around your juniors"!
Is that supposed to be about me?
Sorry, that's wrong!
You were struggling with that,
so I looked it up for you!
Well, cut it out!
Why? You opened up to me about it.
I didn't mean it!
Um, you guys!
Uh-huh?
We're live!
I really didn't!
All of this is reaching the airwaves!
Time's up! The answer is...
this!
Top ways to get slim easily
"Top ways to get slim easily"...
Eek!
So you're on a diet?
Yeah, but...
Dear, everyone got it wrong! Which means...
Hell Power...
Up!
I didn't ask for it to go this far!
They're getting closer and closer
to the lava, and that's real trouble.
Drafts
Post
Don't make Lilly fall!
#OnceMore
#HellsQuiz
Toko-chan is cute
Next will be a Hell VCR Quiz.
#OnceMore
#HellsQuiz
Bernard is going too far
#OnceMore
#HellsQuiz
Guess who is responsible
for sneakily eating everyone's cakes.
Oh, I bought those!
You bought cakes?
Yeah, for all of us to eat together.
And someone ate them...
Just who is the one responsible?
Oh no, what now?
They're gonna find out it was me!
Lililula palilula, end the quiz already!
Here comes the dragon!
Cut it out!
It was me! I did it! I'm sorry!
That's correct!
But as punishment for stealing their food...
the glass will break.
This has gotten real bad.
Now for the final question
you've been waiting for...
A Comeback Quiz!
COMEBACK QUIZ
Whoever gets this right
will progress 100 miles at once!
The roulette will decide
who answers this question!
HELL'S ROULETTE
Lilly
Lulu
Sena
Toko
Toko-san, you're the lucky contestant!
Why do you keep targeting me?!
Now for the question.
Who was Kandachi Toko's first love?
What kind of question is that?!
Hurry up and answer!
Ouch!
State your answer!
M-My pet dog Yasshi!
Unfortunately, that's wrong!
But it is Yasshi!
There has to be something I can do.
Right, magic!
No good! No good!
What now? What now?
This is bad!
I left my wand behind...
Try again, state your answer!
This is your last chance! Go ahead!
Knock it off already!
She already told you it was Yasshi!
Sena!
There I go.
Umm...
Wrap it up somehow!!!
W-We apologize for the indecent display.
There was a mistake with our previous question.
Let's try again: this is the final question,
and your chance to make a big comeback!
The name of your agency is Production... what?
Go on! Answer, answer!
Me! Me! I know!
Contestants, state your answer!
Ready, and...
Once More!
Bingo! That's correct!
WIN
Congratulations
Everyone wins! Congratulations!
Your long journey now reaches its end.
The quiz show Treasure on the Waves
hopes to have you again for another adventure!
Farewell!
Farewell...
Treasure on the Waves
Tune in next time!
Bye-bye!
Thank you!
That Hell's Quiz sure was crazy.
They can really do anything.
#HellsQuiz
Trends
For You
News
Entertainment
#OnceMore
Yamayama Line Delays
Trending in Entertainment
Trending in Japan
What made you think any of that was okay?!
What if something had happened
to those girls?
Seriously, don't do that.
My deepest apologies.
It really felt like I was possessed by something.
Why, you...
Miss Producer.
Huh?
Those were the highest ratings we've ever gotten?
We'll let you off this time.
But watch yourself.
Really, what was that?
Good work.
Today was tough, wasn't it?
Good work to you too.
Get some good rest, okay?
We will.
I need a massage before I go home...
That was freaky.
I was so nervous!
I'm so sweaty...
They're back!
It's over!
Th-That was something...
Quiz shows are more than meets the eye.
Are quiz shows normally like that?
I feel like I pushed myself hard.
But it was very fun... I think?
I thought we were gonna die.
Toko, you almost broke down in tears.
You were making a funny face too, Sena!
Was I really?
Well, we were all terrified.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, who was your first love anyways, Toko-san?
You wanna know?
It was...
There was no such thing!
More importantly,
about those cakes I put in the fridge...
You glutton.
Our cakes...
I'm so sorry!
Alright.
I'm sorry! They just looked so good!
We'll go buy more!
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
It's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
(My dream!)
I just wanna know what the future holds
(Alone!)
Even if the stars in a moonless sky
Still twinkle
(No magic!)
Even if the clouds in a sunless sky
Still drift
I feel so lonely
(I was always right beside you)
I'm searching for you
I'll frame a photo of us two and hang it up
Let's set things the way we want, the way we will, the way they are
Take our chemistry, plus+, minus-, multiplied×, divided÷ by...
I love it every way
Calling me, calling you
(And you)
I want to walk up the stairs of the future with you
Lucky lucky shiny, our beating hearts dreamin' away
If there's clear skies tomorrow, everything will be okay
Maybe I'm a bit sad and weak
(But I'm happy!)
But when I'm with you I feel safe
There's no such thing as wasted time
Let's wait until the rain stops
Check it out, look up at the sky
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
That's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
What kind of future will the spotlight shine on?
Nothing Screams Summer Like a Training Camp